- → healer1064729@gmail.com
- +46855923479
- ☆ Stockholm, Sweden
- 27 years old

Languages

English
Skills
ReactJS
V - 15
VueJS
NextJS
HTML
CSS
InvaSerint
JavaScript
ES6
TypeScript
РНР
NodeJS
Nouejs

Laravel

Daniel Yin

Front End Developer with a keen eye for detail

Senior Front End Developer with 6 years of hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications.

Translate designs to front-end code, estimate time and costs, and determine developer requirements and specifications.

Work experience

Frontend developer

2016/07 - 2017/08 Epic Games, Inc. Cary, North Carolina

Epic Games is an Online Game Company. As a Front End Developer, my core activities included:

- Building stable and maintainable codebases using React.
- Collaborating with designers to ensure designs were efficient and technically sound.
- Assisting with the transition from a waterfall method to the more efficient agile methodology.

Front-end developer

2017/08 - 2019/05 blitz GG Los Angeles, California

- Your personal gaming coach for League of Legends, Valorant, CSGO, Fortnite and more— powered by AI and built with professional players.
- I attended to develop blitz.gg website for Blitz fans as a frontend developer

Front-end developer

2019/06 - 2021/11 Decormatters, Inc. in Milpitas, California

Decormatters is an interior design company. As the Frontend developer, my core activities included:

- Leveraging responsive web frameworks to complete deliverables ahead of schedule.
- Recommending solutions for a user-friendly interface with the design team.
- I was responsible for Dashboard, Detail and Blog pages.

Education

Bachelor of Science

2012 - 2016 Wuhan University Wuhan, Hubei